http://www.control4.com/company/privacy-and-security

PRIVATE AND SECUREBY DESIGNWe’re committed...to earning and maintaining customer trust by focusing on six key principles in everything we do.PrivacyWe respect your privacy; what happens in your home stays in your home.ControlWe put you in control of your privacy with easy-to-use tools and clear choices.TransparencyWe are transparent about data collection and use so you can make informed decisions.SecurityWe protect the data you entrust to us with strong, industry-leading security.Strong legal protections and rightsWe respect your local privacy laws and fight for legal protection of your privacy as a fundamental human right.Benefits to youWhen we do collect data, we use it to benefit you and improve your experiences.PRIVATEWe respectyour privacyThe collection of certain data is essential to the function of a smart home—its collection and use is what makes a home “smart.” For example, the collection of a device’s IP address or other identification number is required to allow those smart devices to communicate with each other in ways that add convenience to your life.The secure storage and appropriate use of that collected data are of the utmost importance to Control4. We're committed to strict and proactive standards for data privacy, because we believe trust must be earned. We respect your right to privacy and believe your data should be handled with integrity and confidence. This is why Control4 continuously evaluates and adjusts our security and privacy practices to ensure your data is protected and used appropriately. See our full privacy policy here.TRANSPARENTYour informationand your rightsData collected is used to provide core functions of a Control4 system, troubleshoot with your system or account, send notifications and relevant technical communications, and to improve the functionality of our products. The information we collect is spelled out in our privacy policy.Control4 does not sell or rent your personal information to third-party companies. Some of your personal information may be shared with partners who assist us in selling, delivering, and installing products and services, for example: Processing credit card payments Shipping and delivering products Fulfilling orders Managing or hosting customer data Assessing your satisfaction and interest in our products and services These partners are obligated to adhere to the same principles and agreements defined in our privacy policy, and Control4 requires these partners to provide assurance of adequate data protection.In order to deliver products and services around the world, we use a network of highly qualified, independent professionals to sell, install, and service your systems. The smart home professionals who work with Control4 are held to high standards and have strict requirements regarding certifications and experience in order to become an authorized Control4 Dealer. At your request, Control4 can help you locate authorized dealers near you and will share the information you provide with the candidates—then you choose which professional you want to work with.At any time Control4 customers have the right to: Be provided with a copy of your personal information held by us. Request the correction or deletion of your personal information held by us. Request that your personal information be transferred to a third party. Withdraw consent for the collection of personal data. Our advisement, as well as information on how to make the above requests, can be found in our privacy policy.SECUREWe protect your dataControl4 engineers and security personnel are proactive in safeguarding customer data. We build products following industry standards and secure methods. We use a variety of methods to continuously improve the security of our customers, dealers, and organization. We are armed with an array of security tools that protect and monitor for threats 24/7. We stay in close alignment with law enforcement and monitor smart home industry threat vectors. We regularly update the security of customer, dealer, and organization systems through patches, configuration changes, and notifications to dealers. We continually collaborate internally on a daily basis to keep products, apps, websites, and services safe for all customers and dealers. SECURITY RESEARCHERS AND PARTNERSTell us your concernswe're listeningWhether you are a security researcher, dealer, or customer, if you think you have found a security issue or vulnerability, we would appreciate your help and ask that you disclose this information responsibly. We are committed to using any information you provide to improve our solutions. Please exercise care if you want to modify any systems or data, so that you don’t degrade the performance or security of any of your systems or data.Report security issues or vulnerabilitiesUse the form below to report issues or vulnerabilities. We will work to assess your report as quickly as possible.Thank you cyber security researchers and white hats.Where is the security vulnerability? Choose one Website Mobile Application Device Control4 Office Location Other
Submit This form uses Invisible reCAPTCHA by Google Privacy Policy  and
Terms of Use Submit This form uses Invisible reCAPTCHA by Google Privacy Policy  and
Terms of Use Submit This form uses Invisible reCAPTCHA by Google Privacy Policy  and
Terms of Use Submit This form uses Invisible reCAPTCHA by Google Privacy Policy  and
Terms of Use Submit This form uses Invisible reCAPTCHA by Google Privacy Policy  and
Terms of Use
